import { Exercise } from ".";

export const ZODIAC: Exercise[] = [
  {
    "question": "Овен",
    "answer": "Ovien",
    "extra": "♈"
  },
  {
    "question": "Телец",
    "answer": "Tiełec",
    "extra": "♉"
  },
  {
    "question": "Близнецы",
    "answer": "Blizniety",
    "extra": "♊"
  },
  {
    "question": "Рак",
    "answer": "Rak",
    "extra": "♋"
  },
  {
    "question": "Лев",
    "answer": "Lew",
    "extra": "♌"
  },
  {
    "question": "Дева",
    "answer": "Diewa",
    "extra": "♍"
  },
  {
    "question": "Весы",
    "answer": "Wiesy",
    "extra": "♎"
  },
  {
    "question": "Скорпион",
    "answer": "Skorpion",
    "extra": "♏"
  },
  {
    "question": "Стрелец",
    "answer": "Strzelec",
    "extra": "♐"
  },
  {
    "question": "Козерог",
    "answer": "Kozierog",
    "extra": "♑"
  },
  {
    "question": "Водолей",
    "answer": "Wodoliej",
    "extra": "♒"
  },
  {
    "question": "Рыбы",
    "answer": "Ryby",
    "extra": "♓"
  }
];
